http://www.standsonline.com/privacy.aspx

0
TV Stands30 inch TVs and under31- 50 inch TVs51 inch TVs and moreTV Stands With Electric FireplaceFurnitureLiving RoomDining RoomBedroomAccent ChairsSpeaker Stands18" or less19" to 29"30" or MoreCenter Channel Speaker StandsAudio / Video RacksTV Mounts / SwivelsCeiling MountsAll Articulating & Interactive MountsLarge Interactive Mounts (51 inch and more)Medium Interactive Mounts (29 - 50 inch)Small Articulating & Interactive Mounts (29" and under)All Full Motion TV Wall MountsLarge Full Motion Mounts (51 INCH AND MORE)Medium Full Motion Mounts (29 - 50 INCH)Small Full Motion Mounts (29 INCH AND UNDER)All Tilting TV Wall MountsLarge Tilting Mounts (51 INCH AND MORE)Medium Tilting Mounts (29 - 50 INCH)Small Tilting Mounts (29 INCH AND UNDER)All Low Profile - Fixed Wall MountsLarge Low Profile Mounts (51 INCH AND MORE)Medium Low Profile Mounts (29 - 50 INCH)Small Low Profile Mounts (29 INCH AND UNDER)Motorized MountsProjector MountsSpeaker MountsWall Mounted FurnitureShop By BrandBelloChiefFurnitechOmnimountPeerlessSanusVantage PointVTI Audio/Video RacksGlobal United FurnitureSALE
0
0
Customer Service
Privacy Policy
At StandsOnline.com, your satisfaction is what counts. All orders are processed with
extensive care to meet our customer's needs. We appreciate the importance of your
purchase. We are here to make your online shopping experience a great one. At
StandsOnline.com, PERFECTION is the theme of our operation.
We guarantee the LOWEST PRICE. We only select the best quality brands. Our Manufacturing Partners are the best in the business. StandsOnline.com has partnered with major United States based AV manufacturers to bring you the best selection.
We will not, under any circumstances, rent or sell your personal information to third parties.
Thank you for visiting StandsOnline.com. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Note, the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
By E-Mail: admin@standsonline.com
By Phone: (800)990-5520
Fax: (818)391-1977
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
How Can We Help?
Please Wait...
